<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Domenic Santangelo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Domenic Santangelo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Domenic Santangelo; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 21:21:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Marketo Forms 2.0 API To Populate Fields</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/28/use-marketo-forms-2-0-api-to-populate-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 21:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/28/use-marketo-forms-2-0-api-to-populate-fields/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally we want to populate Marketo fields with values we calculate on our side. Perhaps advanced UTM handling, custom Salesforce fields, etc. The Marketo Forms 2.0 API makes this pretty easy. Most of what you need to know lives on this documentation page, but I will give you a couple tips you might not otherwise know.
You can populate UTM codes automatically&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;but think it through. You can have Marketo autopopulate your utm values from the query string in the URL, but what if a user navigates to another page?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interleaving Ad-hoc Tasks in a Scrum Team: Fastpass</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/12/18/interleaving-ad-hoc-tasks-in-a-scrum-team-fast-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 21:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/12/18/interleaving-ad-hoc-tasks-in-a-scrum-team-fast-pass/</guid>
      <description>In theory, full agile/scrum with two-week sprints is a major boon for everyone. Engineering teams agree to what exactly is expected of them, and the business agrees on when to expect their asks to be complete. Reality is of course never quite that simple.
One of the core tenets of scrum is that you don&amp;rsquo;t accept a task into your sprint unless it is fully spec&amp;rsquo;d and completable. For instance, if you get a task to change the text color on the home page, but the new color is not defined, you can&amp;rsquo;t accept that task into your sprint because without that color the task is impossible to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>